<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Shyam Tailor</title>
    <link>https://shyam196.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://shyam196.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://shyam196.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://shyam196.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://shyam196.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://shyam196.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a 2nd year PhD student in Machine Learning at the University of Cambridge, having started in October 2019. I am a member of the Machine Learning Systems group in the Computer Science department, where I am supervised by Dr Nic Lane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research interests focus on enabling edge devices to reason from non-uniformly structured data efficiently. The research in my PhD so far has focused on enabling efficient inference for graph neural networks (GNNs), which have a variety of useful applications which are currently not viable for edge platforms.
I am interested in hardware-software co-design techniques, systems challenges, and applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Bachelor&#39;s dissertation with Dr Robert Harle investigated anonymous human proximity detection techniques for smartphones; similar approaches are now used for COVID-19 contact tracing.
In my Master&#39;s dissertation, with Professor Cecilia Mascolo, I focused on building devices that can listen to your body, and won a highly commended award from the department, and a best paper award at the WellComp workshop at Ubicomp 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
